好的 你已经做好了
All right, you're done.
让我们看一下答案
Let's take a look at the solution.
就像我们的content provider中的测试
Just like in our content provider test,
我们使用getContentResolver方法来根据CONTENT_URI进行查询
we can use get content resolver to
query based upon the content URI.
记住 默认的位置实体的CONTENT_URI
Remember, that the default
location entry content URI
会传递所有的参数到数据库
just passes all of the parameters
into the database.
因此 我们可以容易的构建一个包含指定位置的查询
So, we can easily construct a query
containing the location query
来看看这个位置是否已经在数据库中
to see if it is in the database yet.
记住 默认的位置实体CONTENT_URI
Remember that the default
location entry content URI
传递所有的参数到数据库 因此我们可以容易的构建
passes all of the parameters into
the database, so we can easily construct
容易的构建一个包含指定位置的查询 来看看这个位置是否已经在数据库中
a query containing the location setting
to see if it is in the database yet.
如果不在 这个查询会返回一个空的集合(cursor)
If it's not,
then the query will return an empty set.
然后我们应该插入新的cityName 位置设置 和
And we should insert the new city name,
location setting, and
坐标
coordinates together.
注意 我们将会调用addLocation方法 从Task的 doInBackground方法中
Note that we're calling that ad location
method, from inside doing background.
调用getWeatherDataFromJson方法
Which calls getWeatherDataFromJson.
我们已经取消注释了testAddLocation方法
We've uncommented out the test
ad location function.
现在我们运行测试并且测试都通过了
Now, we'll run our tests,
and our tests all pass.
我们已经为下一步做好了准备
We're ready to move on to the next step.